http://www.lighthouseratings.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Privacy Policy
At Light House Ratings, accessible from http://www.lighthouseratings.com/, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Light House Ratings and how we use it.
If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us through email at Contact@www.lighthouseratings.com
Log Files
Light House Ratings follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services’ analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.
Privacy Policies
You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of Light House Ratings.
Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Light House Ratings, which are sent directly to users’ browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.
Note that Light House Ratings has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
Third Pary Privacy Policies
Light House Ratings’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. You may find a complete list of these Privacy Policies and their links here: Privacy Policy Links.
You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. What Are Cookies?
Children’s Information
Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.
Light House Ratings does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This privacy policy (created with the GDPR Generator) applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Light House Ratings. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.
Consent
By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions.
Please follow & like us :)
Search for:
Recent Posts
UPSers are using the drone to improve the connectivity
How can you use FaceTime for PC?
Rating the shopping experience at the MyLowesLife
Rating the product quality at the DGCustomerFirst
How much is the served meat fresh at the MyWegmansConnect?
Archives
June 2020
May 2020
March 2019
October 2018
July 2018
March 2018
November 2017
30 Jun, 2020
Blog How can you use FaceTime for PC?
22 Jun, 2020
Blog Rating the shopping experience at the MyLowesLife
5 Jun, 2020
Blog Rating the product quality at the DGCustomerFirst
3 Jun, 2020
TwitterSplit Rock Lighthouse, Minnesota pic.twitter.com/vlcj3BSplT— Earths Scenery (@Earths_Scenery) May 21, 2018
This popup will close in: Explore the world with us.Sign up below to get all the inspiring photos, videos, and stories delivered to your email for free, plus special offers.  E-MailSubmitReset
CLOSE
